

# **SIRIPONG VORRAKSA**

Full-Stack Design and Researcher

## **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2021 Master of Science Program in Technopreneurship and

(Expect) Innovation Management

Chulalongkorn University

2013 - 2016 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

### **ABOUT**

Full-stack design and researcher, the combination between user experience design, visual design, interaction design, front-end development and the understanding in research methodologies.

I start work with my passion in these field of work for 7 years since I graduated from high school by being a freelance designer.

I've learned and developed myself from working with varied problems and many talented people. Which these things encourage me to keep developing myself and eager to learn new things and always wanted to work with more challenging problem.



#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

3

## **Product Owner, BECi Corporation Ltd.**

2016 - Present

Perform digital platform design and research under the new business development unit of BEC group (Channel 3) Example Projects :

- Mello, video on demand platform.
- Neko Trips, Japan travelling guide website.
- Channel 3 AR campaign, gifts hunting game, using AR technology as a medium for viewers to be able to interact with the live broadcasting TV.

## WP UX/UI Designer, Words True U Co., Ltd.

2016

Design user experience, performance tracker platform for industry or factory use.

**Full-Stack Designer, Freelancer** 

2013 - Present

## **EXPERTISE**

Innovation R&D UX/UI

Interaction Design

Visual Design Creative

Business Development

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

2018 - Present Co-Founder and Designer, PHUKETPLANET Co., Ltd.

Phuket private tour personalisation platform.

2017 - 2019 Full-Stack Design and Researcher, UX Research Lab

An innovation library focus on research, design and development (R&D) in order to obtain good and quality research results. Including innovations based on the norms of good experience.

2014 - 2015 Co-Founder and Full-Stack Design, WordCap! games

2013 - 2014 Founder and Designer, Siam Audibooks website

Interactive website for sharing an audio books to autistic children. Supported by Siam Commercial Bank Foundation. Qualified to 20 teams final round in "SCB Community Project". Published in DMA Magazine and in Sci and Tech TV shows on ThaiPBS, 24 November 2013.

#### CONTACT

**(**+66)89 864 8284

in www.linkedin.com/in/vorraksa

www.dribbble.com/vorraksa

www.vorraksa.com